<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Bradford Malbon on Bradford Malbon - Flute Repair</title>
    <link>https://bsmalb.github.io/bradford/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Bradford Malbon on Bradford Malbon - Flute Repair</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2024 11:00:12 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://bsmalb.github.io/bradford/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Flute Repair Services</title>
      <link>https://bsmalb.github.io/bradford/repair-services/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2024 11:00:12 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://bsmalb.github.io/bradford/repair-services/</guid>
      <description>Last Update - January 2025 Clean, Oil, and Adjust (COA) - Service Description This is the service you need if your flute just doesn’t quite seem to be playing as well as it used to. For flutes that are played a lot this is typically an annual service. COA service is for flutes that have been well maintained. If a flute has been damaged or has not been serviced for many years, then more work will be required to bring that flute back to optimal performance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>https://bsmalb.github.io/bradford/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2024 10:59:58 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://bsmalb.github.io/bradford/about/</guid>
      <description>update&#xA;Bradford Malbon – Flute Maker and Repair Person Bradford earned a B.S. in Music and Mathematics at the College of William and Mary in 2005 and a Master of Music in flute performance from UNLV Las Vegas in 2007. During his college years Bradford began his training in flute making and repair during summer workshops with John Landell. After graduation from college, Bradford began work as a flute finisher at Powell Flutes in the Boston area.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://bsmalb.github.io/bradford/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Dec 2024 13:59:39 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://bsmalb.github.io/bradford/contact/</guid>
      <description>For First Time Clients Before I can accept and begin work on your instrument, I&amp;rsquo;ll need the following information from you. You can make both our lives easier by providng this information in your intial email to me! For returning clients, please inform me of any changes or updates.&#xA;Your Name (First and Last) E-mail address Phone Number Preferred Communication Method (email, phone, text message, etc.) Mailing Address (particularly if shipping will be required) Flute Make and Model Your Service Request (What’s wrong with your flute?</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
